ALES International Labor Records 5225 I
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ALES International Labor Records
1926-1937
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Labor Education Service (ALES)
5225 I
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8209460
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
A. Holland-Loucks, August 02, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5225: ALES Records 5225 C: ALES Course Materials 5225 E: ALES Labor Education Records 5225 L: ALES Labor Plays 5225 S: ALES Scrapbooks 5225 MB: ALES Pearl L. Willen Memorial Memorabilia
American Labor Education Service
8209460
- General No. 1 of 2, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Danish
- General No. 2 of 2, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Worker's Educational Association No. 1 of 2, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Workers' Educational Association No. 2 of 2, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Danish Trade Unions, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Social Reform and some Material on Laws No. 1 of 4, 1934-1936 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Social Reform and some Material on Laws No. 2 of 4, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Social Reform and some Material on Laws No. 3 of 4, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Social Reform and some Material on Laws No. 4 of 4, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Agriculture - Also Cooperatives, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- The International People's College, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Worker's Summer Schools and Year Round, 1926-1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)